A Guide to the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 1999-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series VI: Secure Commonwealth Panel Files, 2001-2005
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files, 2001-2005
    - Citizen & Commonwealth Sub Panel, 2002-2004 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Preparedness Work Group
      - 2003-2004 (Folder 1) (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 2004 (Folder 2) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - First Responder Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2005 (Folder 1) (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2005 (Folder 2) (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Suporting Documentation, 2003-2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - First Responders Leadership Conference, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Funding Task Force, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Government Operations & Funding Sub Panel, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Health & Medical Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Documentation, 2002-2004 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Industry & Commerce Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2002-2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Supporting Documentation, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Intelligence & Information Sharing Task Force
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - 2002-2005 (Folder 2) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Mass Fatalities Task Force, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - National Strategy for Homeland Security, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Panel Recommendations & Progress Reports
      - 2001-2002 (Folder 1) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - 2002-2003 (Folder 2) (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Performance Measures Task Force, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Public Hearings, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Public/Private Cooperation Task Force
      - 2004-2005 (Folder 1) (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Secure Virginia Initiative
      - Background Files, 2002-2003 (Folder 1) (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - 2002 (Folder 2) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Stakeholder Forum, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Strategic Plan
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Task Force Administration, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Technology Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Supporting Documentation, 2001-2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Transportation Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Supporting Documentation, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Utilities Sub Panel
      - Meeting Minutes, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Supporting Documentation, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Public Safety Terrorism Summit, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Subseries B: Meeting Files, 2002-2005
    - 2002
      - March 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - April 5 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - May 9 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - June 7 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Aug. 8-9
        - Folder 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - Folder 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - Folder 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Folder 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Sept. 5 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Oct. 15
        - Folder 1 (Box 21)
        - Folder 2 (Box 21)
      - Nov. 21
        - Folder 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Folder 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Dec. 17 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 2003
      - May 23
        - Folder 1 (Box 22)
        - Folder 2 (Box 22)
      - June 20
        - Folder 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - Folder 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Aug. 22
        - Folder 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - Folder 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Oct. 31
        - Folder 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - Folder 2 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Dec. 18
        - Folder 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - Folder 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - Folder 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 2004
      - June 23
        - Folder 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - Folder 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Aug. 25
        - Folder 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - Folder 2 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Sept. 21 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Oct. 7 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 2005
      - March 9
        - Folder 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - May 11
        - Folder 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - July 13
        - Folder 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Folder 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Oct. 4 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Series VII: Supporting Documentation, 1999-2005
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files, 2001-2005
    - Appropriations Committee, 2005 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Aviation, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Bioterrorism Grant Application
      - 2002 (Folder 1) (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - 2002 (Folder 2) (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - 2002 (Folder 3) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Boy Scout Jamboree, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Citizen Corps, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Delegation, 2002-2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Continuity of Government and Operations, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Decision Briefs, 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Department of Homeland Security Information Technology & Evaluation Program
      - 2004 (Folder 1) (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - 2004 (Folder 2) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Election Security, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Evaluation & Exercise Program (Office of Domestic Preparedness)
      - 2004 (Folder 1) (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 2004 (Folder 2) (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Gilmore Commission
      - First Responders Reports, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Records, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Sub Panel Reports, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Gubernatorial Appointments, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security Advisory Council, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Homeland Security Information Network, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Hurricane Isabel, 2003-2004 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Legislation
      - 2002
        - Budget Proposals (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - House (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Senate (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - 2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - 2005
        - Folder 1 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Folder 2 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum of Agreement, 2002-2005 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - National Security Project
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - National Guard General Information, 2001-2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - PROTECT Virginia Sessions, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Real ID Task Force
      - November 2, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - December 7, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Speeches, 2003-2005 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Testimony, 2004-2005 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - VERTEX After-Action Report, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University Business Roundtable, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Defense Industrial Authority, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute
      - 2003-2004 (Folder 1) (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 2003 (Folder 2) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Subseries B: Base Realignment and Closure, 2003-2005
    - Cecil Field/Oceana Background Files
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - 2005 (Folder 3) (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - 2005 (Folder 4) (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - 2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - 2004 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 2005
        - Folder 1 (Box 33)
        - Folder 2 (Box 33)
    - Executive Orders, 2004-2005 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Fort Monroe, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Hearings
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Information Sharing & Analysis, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Joint Forces Command, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings, 2003-2005 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Oceana Briefing Material
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Personnel & Staff Contacts, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Presentations
      - 2003 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - 2004
        - Folder 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Folder 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Folder 3 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - 2005
        - Folder 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Folder 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations
      - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - 2005 (Folder 3) (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - 2005 (Folder 4) (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Reports
      - 2004 (Folder 1) (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - 2004 (Folder 2) (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Statements/Briefing Points, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commission on Military Bases
      - Briefing Book, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Meetings
        - 2003
          - August 12 (Box 36, Folder 5)
          - October 10 (Box 36, Folder 6)
          - November 20 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - 2004
          - January 9 (Box 36, Folder 8)
          - March 17 (Box 36, Folder 9)
          - April 16 (Box 36, Folder 10)
          - April 28 (Box 36, Folder 11)
          - May 27 (Box 36, Folder 12)
          - July 16 (Box 36, Folder 13)
          - August 4 (Box 36, Folder 14)
          - August 18 (Box 36, Folder 15)
          - August 24 (Box 36, Folder 16)
          - October 8 (Box 36, Folder 17)
        - 2005 April 14 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Commission on Military Bases
      - Minutes
        - 2003 December 17 (Box 36, Folder 19)
        - 2004 Sept. 14 (Box 36, Folder 20)
        - 2004 Nov. 18 (Box 36, Folder 21)
        - 2005 April 28 (Box 36, Folder 22)
        - 2005 June 29 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Working Groups, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: Homeland Security Grant Information, 2000-2005
    - DOTS Exercise, 2003-2005 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Funding Task Force, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Grant Awards, 2003-2004 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Grant Correspondence
      - 2002-2003 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - 2004 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - 2004 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - 2005 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Grant Information
      - FY 1999
        - 2000 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - FY 2001, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - FY 2002
        - 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Supplemental, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - FY 2003
        - 2003 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - State Homeland Security Grant Program II, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - FY 2004, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Grant Information Guide, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Grant Reports/Papers, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Interoperability Grant, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Iraq Hostilities, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - News Releases, 2002-2003 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Office for Domestic Preparedness Information, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Presentations, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Urban Areas Security Initiative (UASI)
      - Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Meeting Information
        - 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - 2004 (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - 2004 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Presentations, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Worksheets, 2003-2005 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Port Authority Grant
      - 2002 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - 2002 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Worksheets, 2003-2005 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: National Capital Region Documents, 2002-2005
    - 2002
      - January (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - July (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - August (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - September (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - October (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - November (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - December (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 2003
      - January (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - February (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - March (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - April (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - May (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - June
        - Folder 1 (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - Folder 2 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - July (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - August (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - September
        - Folder 1 (Box 42)
        - Folder 2 (Box 42)
      - October (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - November (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - December (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 2004
      - January (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - February (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - March (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - April (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - May (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - June (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - July (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - September (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - October (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - November (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - December (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - 2005
      - January (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - March (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - April (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - May (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - June
        - Folder 1 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Folder 2 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - July (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - August (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Subseries E: Office Projects, 1999-2005
    - Byrne Grant
      - 2002 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - 2003 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - 2004 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - 2005 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP)
      - Certifications
        - 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - 2004 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - 2005 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Plans
        - 2002 (Folder 1) (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - 2002-2003 (Folder 2) (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Special Project with SRA International, Inc. 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - State COOP Planning Assessment
        - 2005 (Folder 1) (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - 2005 (Folder 2) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Driver Licensing & Identification Card Issuance Task Force
      - Action Statements, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Background, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Meeting Notes, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Task Force on Domestic Preparedness
      - 1999 (Folder 1) (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - 1999 (Folder 2) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Presentations
      - 2002-2005 (Folder 1) (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - 2002-2005 (Folder 2) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Secure Virginia Initiative Reports
      - 1999-2001 (Folder 1) (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - 1999-2001 (Folder 2) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel
      - 1999-2001 (Folder 1) (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - 1999-2001 (Folder 2) (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - 2000-2001 (Folder 3) (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Background Information
        - 2001 (Folder 1) (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - 2001 (Folder 2) (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - 2001 (Folder 3) (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Reports, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Public Safety Terrorism Summit, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 6)